MATFUSZ ZARFMBA

Wroclaw, Poland

Email address: matzaremba@icloud.com

Nationality: Polish (citizen of the EU/EEA Member States)

GitHub link: https://github.com/matzar

Portfolio link: https://mateuszzaremba.weebly.com/portfolio.html
LinkedIn link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mateusz-zaremba/

Personal Profile

A highly motivated and enthusiastic individual with 3 years of learning experience in C++ 11/14/17 and Unity3D programming plus almost 1 year of professional software and game development; skilled in agile, pair and SCRUM software development, able to adapt to any given situation with a professional approach. Learns quickly using existing experience and environments, to integrate as a productive member of a team. Employs strong organisational skills, ever ready to learn and develop new skills and is always happy to take a flexible approach to work. Works to target effectively and possesses analytical and organisational skills together with excellent written and oral communication.

Technical Skills (Please press link to access github repository)

Core:

- <u>C++</u>
- Unity3D using C#
- Unreal Engine 4
- Visual Studio, Xcode, VS Code, Atom
- github BASH, git SVN, SVN
- JIRA, Confluence, Crucible, Bamboo

Additional:

- OpenGL 1.1 | DirectX 11 HLSL
- Networking with SFML/UE4
- PSVita with Box2D using C++
- Face emotion recognition semi-ML
- SQL
- Visual Novel made with Ren'Py using Python

Education

University of Abertay Dundee, United Kingdom:

2015 - 2018 Bachelor of Science in Computer Game Applications Development, 2:1 (link to academic transcript):

3rd year modules (GPA: 2.83):

- Graphics Programming with Shaders (C+)
- Gameplay Mechanics Development (C+)
- Network Systems for Game Development (A)
- Artificial Intelligence (B)
- Professional Team Project: Planning and Prototyping (C+)
- Professional Team Project: Development and Delivery (C+)

2nd year modules (GPA: 4.17)

- Data Structures and Algorithms 1 (A)
- Data Structures and Algorithms 2 (A+)
- Graphics Programming (A)
- Game Programming and System Architectures (A)
- Film and Game Genres (A)
- Mathematics for Application Development 2 (A+)

$\mathbf{1}^{\text{st}}$ year modules (GPA: 3.63):

- Computer and Graphics Architectures (A)
- Programming in C++ (A)
- Narrative Theory in Interactive Game Design (C+)
- Mathematics for Applications Development 1 (A+)
- Asset Production for Games (B+)
- Games for Change (B+)

Sep 2015 - Jul 2018:

Member of Abertay Game Development Society (git: 1st year, 2nd year)

Sep 2015 - Apr 2016:

Class Representative for 1st Year Computer Applications Game Development course

Relevant Experience

01.2019 - 02.2019: C++ Software Engineer Intern, First Line Software

- Design and implementation of large distributed IT systems according to customer and project requirements.
- Quick and efficient concept creation and prototyping of new solutions.
- Close co-operation with product management to understand the requirements of customers and deliver the agreed solution on time
- Testing of the developed solution

08.2018 - 10.2018: Unreal Game Programmer Intern, Bohemia Interactive

- Project worked on Vigor (video update I worked on), post-apocalyptic survival game
- Engine: UE4 | Platform: XBOX ONE

Key responsibilities:

- Networked gameplay programming
- UI programming
- Developing new solutions based on already existing ones and bug fixing

09.2017 - 06.2018: Lead Programme, Abertay University: Professional Project

- Project worked on Mobile game for Junkfish Game Company | Retro platformer for Timex company (git)
- Engine: Unity | Programming language: C# | Platforms: Android (Junk Fish) | Windows (Timex)

Key responsibilities:

- Prototyping and gameplay programming
- Source control maintenance (merging, pull requests, .gitignore)
- Programming team management using GitHub Projects with kanban board, SCRUM (Deadlines setting, mentoring)

Game Jams

24.01.2018 - 26.01.2018: Gameplay Programmer/Design/Team Lead, Serious Game Jam

- Mobile game prototype aiding lectures and students at the University of St Andrews with practical exercises preparation and explanation
- Engine: Unity | Programming language: C# | Platform: Android (video link, git)

15.11.2017: Gameplay Programmer/Design/Team Lead, AGDS 4-hour Game Jam

- Brief visual novel with animations, presenting a joke, made in 4-hours with two artists
- Engine: Ren'Py | Programming language: Python | Platform: Windows (video link, git)

15.08.2016 – 17.08.2016: Gameplay Programmer/Design/Team Lead, Rainbow Game Jam

- Infinite runner chosen to be made in 48-hours with two other artists and a sound designer
- Engine: Unity | Programming language: C# | Platforms: Windows, MAC, Linux (video link, git, play game)

29.01.2016 - 31.01.2016: Gameplay Programmer, Global Game Jam 2016

- Easy pick-up game. My first Unity game and first game jam
- Engine: Unity | Programming language: C# | Platforms: Windows, MAC, Linux (video link)

Other Experience

Oct 2015 – Dec 2015: Warden, St. Ninian's Institute, Diocese of Dunkeld

Taking care of the St Ninian's Institute and its guests; welcoming them at the reception and showing to the room.
 Overall maintenance: checking heaters, creating online calendar, reacting to any emergencies

Apr 2015 – Aug 2015: Waiter/Bartender, Drumoig Golf Hotel

 Working behind the bar, waiting tables and welcoming people at the hotel while maintaining professional approach in every situation

May 2013 – Aug 2013: Office Assistant, University of Wroclaw

- Calling vendors to set up appointments and gather information, delivering post, helping out in the office with various

Jan 2009 - Aug 2009: Younger Lifeguard, Wroclaw Water Park

- Taking care of visitors safety and well being. Stamina and health training. Took part in a solo rescue action

Hobbies and interests:

In my spare time I like to go for long walks and play squash. I also keep up to date with current technologies and affairs.

References available on request